Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran School of Art + Design records, circa 1908-2012 COR0009.0.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Dean's records [legacy series], 1890-1983; Series 1
  - Sarah Yerkes records, 1981; Series 1 Subseries 6
    Few items have been deposited at this time. These include one folder on the 1981 Affordable Art sale and an April 1981 report submitted to the Middle States Association of Colleges and Schools for candidacy in that Association (see container listing).
    - Affordable Art Fundraiser, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Middle States Association of Colleges and Schools - Candidate Planning Document, 1981 April; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 9, Folders 7-8)
  - William Barrett records, 1981-1983; Series 1 Subseries 7
    Additional records of William Barrett are located in Series 11 subseries 3 William Barrett records, 1981-1987.
    As of original processing in 1983, few items had been deposited. These include information on the 1981 summer school; the fall 1981 Auction; a letter from Miss Elizabeth Taylor's secretary (May 1982); the 1982 CSA self-study supporting the school's candidacy :in the Middle States Association of Colleges and Schools; and the 1983 report of the school responding to the October 1982 visit and evaluation of MSACS.
    - Correspondence - Elizabeth Taylor Letter, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Great Adentures Auction, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Middle States Association of Colleges and Schools - Self-Study pp. 1-49, 1982 October; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Middle States Association of Colleges and Schools - Self-Study pp. 50-107, 1982 October; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Middle States Association of Colleges and Schools - Self-Study pp. 108-153, 1982 October; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Middle States Association of Colleges and Schools - Self-Study pp.154-202, 1982 October; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Middle States Association of Colleges and Schools - Self-Study NASAD Index, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Middle States Association of Colleges and Schools - Self-Study Appendices A-C, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Middle States Association of Colleges and Schools - Self-Study Appendix D, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Middle States Association of Colleges and Schools - Self-Study, Appendices E-F, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Post Accreditation Report on MSACS Evaluation, 1983; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Summer School, 1981; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Dean's records, 1968-2003; Series 11
  Arranged in 7 subseries: Roy slade records, 1968-1977; Peter Thomas records, 1978-1982; William Barrett records, 1981-1987; Bruce Yenawine records, 1984-1990; David Levy records, 1989-2003; Samuel Hoi records, 1989-2000; and Kirk Pillow records, 1984-2001.
  Additional dean records, processed by the Corcoran Archives in 1983, are located in Series 1 Dean's records [legacy series], 1890-1983.
  Includes records generated by and maintained by the Dean's office of the Corcoran School of Art transferred to the Corcoran Archives following the initial processing of the archives in 1983. Materials include accredidation records, Board of Trustees and Executive Committee Meeting reports, budget files, commencement files, committee records, correspondence, curriculum files, faculty reports, grant files, memos, self-study materials, space study records, student and alumni surveys, and subject files, dating from 1968-2003.
  - Roy Slade records, 1968-1977; Series 11 subseries 1
    Additional records of dean Roy Slade are located in Series 1 subseries 4 Roy Slade records, 1968-1977.
    Contains records of Roy Slade, Dean of the Corcoran School from 1970-1977. Materials include correspondence, curriculum files, memos, and self-study materials, dating from 1968-1977.
    - Full-Time Students Fall and Spring, 1971-1972; Series 11 subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Courses Fall & Spring: Syllabi, Rosters, 1970-1971; Series 11 subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Printed Material, 1970-1971; Series 11 subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Mimeographed Material, circa 1970s; Series 11 subseries 1 (Box 32, Folders 4-5)
    - Margot Wade, 1968-1970; Series 11 subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Corcoran School Policy, 1968-1969; Series 11 subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Mimeographed Material Registrar's Office, circa 1970s; Series 11 subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - The Dupont Center, 1976-1977; Series 11 subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Corcoran Dupont Center 3rd and 4th Year Fine Arts, circa 1970s; Series 11 subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Roy Slade, Self-Study September, 1973; Series 11 subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Peter Thomas records, 1977-1982; Series 11 subseries 2
    Files are arranged alphabetically.
    Additional records of dean Peter Thomas are located in Series 1 subseries 2 Peter Thomas records, 1974-1980.
    Contains records of Peter Thomas, Dean of the Corcoran School from 1977-1980. Materials include accreditation reports, budget records, curriculum files, and faculty reports, dating from 1977-1982.
    - Academic Classes, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Academic Curriculum, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Budget, 1971-1974; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Budget, 1975-1976; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Proposed Budget, 1975-1977; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Budget, 1976-1977; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Proposed Budget, 1976-1977; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Revised Budget, 1976-1977; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Budgets and Audit, 1976-1978; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Budget, 1979-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Curriculum, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Dupont Center Building, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Faculty Complaints, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Faculty - Dismissed, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Faculty Warning Letters, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Faculty Manual, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Faculty Reports, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Faculty Salaries, 1968-1978; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Financial Sub Committee, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Ford Grant Papers, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Ford Foundation 5th Yr Grant, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Foundation Curriculum, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - GW Transfer Problems, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Graduation, 1979-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Graphic Design, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - NASA Materials, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - NASA Conferences, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - NASA - Misc., circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - NASA/CSA, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - NEA Visiting Artists, 1980-1981; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Open Program Studies, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Open Program, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - Pedestal Room, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 33)
    - Photo Dept., circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 34)
    - Photo Model Releases, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 35)
    - P.R., circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 36)
    - Telephone Number & Lists, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 37)
    - Sculpture Competition, 1979; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 38)
    - UICA, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 39)
    - Course Syllabus & Booklist, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 40)
    - Bi-monthly Reports, 1980-1981; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 41)
    - BFA Impact Study, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 42)
    - DOE - Energy Grants, 1981; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 43)
    - Heads of Dept - etc., circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 44)
    - Saza - Executive Committee Information, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 45)
    - Maine, 1981; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 46)
    - Schedules & Space, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 47)
    - Sculpture Competition, 1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 48)
    - Sculpture, 1981; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 49)
    - Press/Various, 1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 50)
    - School PR Log, 1981; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 51)
    - Boys Club, 1982 June 4; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 52)
    - Catalogue, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 53)
    - Graduation, 1982; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 54)
    - High School Art, circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 55)
    - Maine, 1982; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 56)
    - Application to Award Degrees (D.C. License Comission), circa 1977-1980; Series 11 subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 57)
  - William Barrett records, 1981-1987; Series 11 subseries 3
    Additional records of dean William Barrett are located in Series 1 subseries 7 William Barrett records, 1981-1983.
    Contains records of William Barrett, Dean of the Corcoran School from 1981-1987. Materials include accredidation records, correspondence, memos, and space study records, dating from 1981-1987.
    - Governance and Maintenance Accreditation, 1982; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Goals and Objectives Accreditation, 1982; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Visitor's Report Self-Study, 1984; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - RONA, circa 1980s; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - School Accreditation MSA, circa 1980s; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - School Accreditation, 1982-1983; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Middle States, 1984-1985; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - NASAD Procedures for Institutional Membership, circa 1980s; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Dean's Report, 1988-1989; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Space Studies, 1986; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Building plans, 1981-1982; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Degree Papers, 1977-1978; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Bill Barrett, 1984-1987; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Philosophy Applicants, 1985; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - MFA, circa 1985; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - ELIC, 1984-1985; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Memos to All Staff, 1985; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - SRA; Credit Union, 1985-1986; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Graphic Design Conference, 1986; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Dean's Report to..., 1987 May 18; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Dean's Correspondence File, 1985 January-December; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - George Washington University, 1985; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Mount Vernon Exchange, 1984-1987; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Computer Material, 1985; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Student Survey, 1981-1985; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - General Operations Meetings, 1987; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Personal, circa 1985; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Remarks, circa 1985; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Faculty Meetings + Memos, circa 1985; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - School Payment to Gallery I, circa 1985; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - School Payment to Gallery II, circa 1985; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Five Year Plan, 1982; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - Goals and Objectives, 1977-1983; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - Dean's Correspondence, 1987-1988; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - Diodatti, circa 1985; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - Doug Lang - Correspondence, circa 1985; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - Dean's Correspondence File, 1984 July-December; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 30)
    - Dean's Correspondence, 1984 January-July; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 31)
    - Bill Barrett's Correspondence, 1983; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 32)
    - Memorandums - Dean, 1983; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 33)
    - Downtown Partnership, circa 1985; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 34)
    - Johnston Sculpture Competition, circa 1985; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 35)
    - Housing Contract for Competition, circa 1985; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 36)
    - Misc., circa 1985; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 37)
    - Johnston Sculpture Brochure Requests, circa 1985; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 38)
    - Johnston Poster Info., 1985; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 39)
    - Johnston Competition, 1984-1986; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 40)
    - Competition Applications, circa 1985; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 41)
    - Prints, circa 1985; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 42)
    - Invitation, Press Release, Registrant Information, etc., circa 1985; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 43)
    - Supplies, Information, circa 1985; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 44)
    - Jury, circa 1985; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 45)
    - Applicants; Acceptances, 1983; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 46)
    - Materials Fees Received, circa 1985; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 47)
    - Competition Invitees, 1984; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 48)
    - Johnston Letters, Memos, 1985; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 49)
    - Applicants Acceptance, 1979-1982; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 50)
    - Poster, 1983; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folders 51-52)
    - Barry Johnston Sculpture, circa 1985; Series 11 subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 53)
  - Bruce Yenawine records, 1984-1990; Series 11 subseries 4
    Contains records of Bruce Yenawine, Dean of the Corcoran School from 1988-1990. Materials include acccreditation records, Board of Trustees and Executive Committee Meeting reports, committee records, self-study materials, and student and alumni surveys, dating from 1984-1990.
    - Accreditation, 1989; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Self-Study Steering Committee Minutes, 1989 May 2; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Steering Committee, 1989 May; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Self-Study Subcommittees Outlines, 1989; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Institutional Integreity Mission, Goals, and Objectives Michael Wyatt, Chair, 1989; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Organization and Administration Governing Board, Sis Hedden, Chair, 1989; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Program & Curricular Outcomes Innovation and Experimentation, Rona Slade, Chair, 1989; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - The Faculty, Bernie Welt, Chair, 1989; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Admissions Student Services, Amy Stewart, Chair, 1989; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Planning, Budgetting, Accounting, Cartan Kraft, Chair, 1989; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Library/Learning Resources, Ann McGinnis, Chair, 1989; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Plant & Equipment, Bruce Yenawine, 1989; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Faculty Record Report, 1989-1990; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Planning Questionnaries Self-Study, 1989-1990; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Report Drafts Self Study, 1989-1990; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Self Study.. Retention Case Study, 1989-1990; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Students Hx-, 1989-1990; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Alum Outcome Surveys, 1989-1990; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Mission, Goals, & Objectives, Outcomes/Planning, 1989-1990; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Student Services/Admissions, 1989-1990; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Student Surveys, 1989; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Alumni Outcome Questionnarie, 1990; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Student Services Survey, 1984; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1989 June 26; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1989 April 24; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1989 January 30; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1989 December 11; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1989 November 20; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1989 October 16; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1989 July 17; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1989 April 10; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1989 March 13; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1989 February 13; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1989 January 9; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Art School Committee Meeting, 1989 May 1; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Art School Committee Meeting, 1989 February 6; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1988 November 28; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1989 September 26; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1988 December 12; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1988 November 14; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1988 October 17; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1988 September 12; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1988 July 18; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Planning Document, circa 1988; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - External Affairs (ASC), 1986-1987; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1988 June 27; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - Art School Committee Meeting, 1988 November 7; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Art School Committee Meeting, 1988 September 14; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - Art School Committee Meeting, 1988 May 31; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 26)
    - Art School Committee Meeting, 1988 February 8; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 27)
    - Art School Committee Meetings, 1985-1987; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Working Groups, circa 1985-1990; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 29)
    - Internal Affairs (ASC), circa 1985-1990; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 30)
    - Facilities (ASC), circa 1985-1990; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 31)
    - Pension Building, circa 1985-1990; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 32)
    - Jackson, circa 1985-1990; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 33)
    - Jackson School, circa 1985-1990; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folders 34-35)
    - Virginia Warehouse, circa 1985-1990; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 36)
    - 3050 R Street Residential Treatment Facility, circa 1985-1990; Series 11 subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - David Levy records, 1989-2003; Series 11 subseries 5
    Additional records of David Levy are located in Corcoran Archives RG 2.0 Directors records Series 24 David Levy reccords, Circa 1990-2006.
    Contains records of David Levy throughout his tenure as Corcoran Director from 1991-2006 specifically related to his role as acting Dean of the Corcoran School in 1991. Materials include accredidation files, budget records, Commencement records, and self-study reports, dating from 1989-2003.
    - Slade, Dean of School and DCL correspondence, 1990; Series 11 subseries 5 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Centennial, 1989; Series 11 subseries 5 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Faculty & Administrative Staff, 1967-1983; Series 11 subseries 5 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Photos Summer, 1987; Series 11 subseries 5 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Convocation, 1990 January 22; Series 11 subseries 5 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Centennial, 1989; Series 11 subseries 5 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Dory Teipel/ Binney & Smith, Inc. Centennial Reunion Gala Nat'l Gallery Program for Teacher Education, 1989; Series 11 subseries 5 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Centennial Reunion Gala Saturday, 1990 May 12; Series 11 subseries 5 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Martin Agency, circa 1990; Series 11 subseries 5 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Dept's Schedules, circa 1990; Series 11 subseries 5 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Art Rental/Sales Gallery, circa 1990; Series 11 subseries 5 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - AICA, circa 1990; Series 11 subseries 5 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - AICA Memos/Correspondence, circa 1990; Series 11 subseries 5 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - AICA Member Schools, circa 1990; Series 11 subseries 5 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - AICA Membership, circa 1990; Series 11 subseries 5 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Marts & Lundy, Inc. Development Survey, circa 1990; Series 11 subseries 5 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - College Facilities AICA - OE, circa 1990; Series 11 subseries 5 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - AICA, circa 1990; Series 11 subseries 5 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Budget/Audit, circa 1990; Series 11 subseries 5 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - AICA Board of Directors Meeting Washington, DC, 1990 January 24-26; Series 11 subseries 5 (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - AICA The Education of Painters: A Symposium/New York City, 1990 May 20-22; Series 11 subseries 5 (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - AIA: Bruce Yenawine, circa 1990; Series 11 subseries 5 (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - AICA New York Studio School, circa 1990; Series 11 subseries 5 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - AICA Film/Video Center, circa 1990; Series 11 subseries 5 (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - National Assemby for Visual Arts Education, circa 1990; Series 11 subseries 5 (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - Helms Amendment, circa 1990; Series 11 subseries 5 (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - Student March Helms Amendment, circa 1990; Series 11 subseries 5 (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - Academic Freedom and Artistic Expression, 1990; Series 11 subseries 5 (Box 56, Folder 28)